José Siopa

Student

Contact

Phone

E-mail

siopajose@outlook.com

Website

https://summyt14.github.io

Technical Profile

- HTML
- JavaScript
- MySQL
- Python
- Kotlin
- Java
- Unreal Engine 5: Blueprints and C++
- Unity 3D: C#
- Blender

Competencies

Game prototypes

Easily learning Programming Languages

Glitch and bug resolution

Coding skills

Teambuilding

Effective communication

Many experience in creating games while working both in a team and individually. I achieve intended concepts according to project requirements by utilizing diverse technology resources, to create games or other applications. I'm committed in listening carefully to critiques and requests, incorporating feedback and boosting project outcomes to surpass expectations.

Work History

2022-02 -

Current

Game Developer

GameDev Técnico, Taguspark, Lisbon

- Developed 2D and 3D video games for PC using Unity 3D and Unreal Engine 5.
- Collaborated with game designers, artists and testers to ensure quality product delivery.
- Designed and implemented gameplay mechanics and interactive elements for multiple titles.
- Improved my programmings skills by participating in game jams.
- GameDev Técnico Webpage:
 https://gamedev.tecnico.ulisboa.pt/

2012-08 -Current

Seasonal Orchard Worker

Family Farm, Alcobaça

- Collaborated with fruit pickers to maximize team productivity and achieve deadlines.
- Operated machinery and equipment safely and responsibly, minimizing risk.
- Quality-assured picked fruits to meet company and industry standards.

Education

2018-08 -2021-08

Bachelor's Degree: Computer Engineering And Multimedia

Instituto Superior De Engenharia De Lisboa - Rua Conselheiro Emídio Navarro 1, 1959-007 Lisboa

2022-09 -Current

Master's Degree: Computer Engineering

Faculdade De Ciências Da Universidade De Lisboa -Campo Grande 016, 1749-016 Lisboa

Additional Information

My released games: https://summyt.itch.io/